Charles Onuoha

I am a self-motivated, passionate and progress-driven 4+ years experienced Web Designer/Administrator in Nigeria with an extensive background in the industry. With a long-standing record of initiative and innovation, I have developed and executed strategies which I believe will bring value to any company.

Throughout the course of my career, I have honed my quality control and inventory abilities. I am an astute problem-solver, good time manager capable of prioritizing and managing complex projects with proficiency.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Komback Blog/Komback Marketplace, Massachusetts, USA — *Web Design/Administrator*

March 2019 - PRESENT

Komback is a free Online Marketplace built for Africa & America.

Our mission is to be Africa's and America's favorite destination for discovering great value and unique selection.

We give sellers the platform, solutions, and support they need to grow their businesses and thrive. Our own Success is measured via our customers' success. Yes and we are transforming the individual selling experience to help you turn the things you no longer need into cash you can use.

We strive to ensure all our users get the Best Experience in Online Marketing...

REF: komback.com

Komback Blog is a media and information service focused on News and Entertainment publishing.

REF: kombackblog.com

ERP Institute, Lagos, Nigeria — Web Configuration/Malware Removing (contract)

July 2018 - September 2018

ERP institute is a Digital Enterprise Company built to bridge the training and knowledge gap in optimal use of ERP solutions by corporate organizations. We connect experienced consultants to individuals and corporations in need of training on ERP solutions like SAP, Oracles, Microsoft Dynamics, SAGE, Odoo etc.

REF: erpinstitute-ng.com

32 Ozumba Mbadiwe Avenue, VI, Lagos, Nigeria,

(+234) 817-860-5332,

<u>charleschidozie1995@gmail.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/charles-harrison</u>

SKILLS

- Passionate and Self-driven
- Good Team Player
- Fast Learner
- Good Listener
- Interpersonnel
- Good Communication Skill
- Good Time Management

LANGUAGES

English, Igbo

PROJECTS

Komback App - App Development for Komback Marketplace

App For Komback Online Marketplace. I used Android Studio and Open Source CMS to Design this App Link: https://bit.ly/KombackAPP

My Magic App - App Development for Africa Magic

App For Africa Magic Entertainment I used Android Studio and Open Source CMS to Design this App Link: https://bit.ly/MyMagicAPP

Equipie Business Marketplace, Lagos, Nigeria — *Malware Removing (contract)*

July 2018 - September 2018

Equipie is focused on Business Marketplace, Franchise and Business Listing. It's a platform where individuals buy and sell Business.

I was hired by Equipie to help them remove malwares which were redirecting visitors to a malicious site.

REF: equipie.com

Harrimedia, Lagos, Nigeria — Founder/Web Design/Administrator

April 2014 - PRESENT

Harrimedia is focused on African Movies, Social Videos, News Media, Trending, Entertainment and more, based in Nigeria for watching Movies and getting Latest News online. Linked to the media which is hosted on 3rd party services (YOUTUBE) to stream Movies. All our Movies are in HTML5.

REF: <u>harrimedia.com</u> <u>harrimedia.com.ng</u>

Wincotech Lift Limited, Lagos, Nigeria — Lift Technician

August 2016 - PRESENT

We are the distributors of Doppler and Arvina lifts in Nigeria.

For many years now, WincoTech Lifts Nigeria Limited have withstood the test of time while maintaining an ever-increasing customer base. Our commitment to quality service and working with our customers to find the most cost-effective solution to their problems has made us one of the leading lift specialists in our field and the No1 choice for many of the Nigerian leading companies.

Vision: To be the preferred Lifts, Escalators and Moving walks Company committed to delivering quality, timely and cost effective services.

Mission: To provide professional services that exceeds client's expectations with high returns on investment for our stakeholders.

Laspo App — App Development for Laspotech

Students App For Lagos State Polytechnic. I used Android Studio and Open Source CMS to design this App.

Link: https://bit.ly/LaspoApp

Charles Web — Web Design | App Design | IT Consultant

My Personal business website for showcasing my Career, Portfolio, Services, Tutorials, Tips sharing etc.

REF:

https://www.charlesweb.com.ng https://learn.charlesweb.com.ng

More Projects at

https://www.charlesweb.com.ng/port folio

EDUCATION

Lagos State Polytechnic, Lagos, Nigeria — National Diploma(Mechanical Engineering)

2014 - 2016

Cisco Networking Academy, Online Vacation Study IoT - Internet of Things (NetaCad)

2017 - 2018

Sololearn Academy, Online Vacation Study — HTML Fundamentals, CSS, MYSQL

2017 - 2018

More Professional Experience can be found at https://www.charlesweb.com.ng